加州  洛杉矶
你们每呼吸一次
With each breath you take,
就都释放一次过往
you release the bonds of the past.
你们往日不再
For you are not your past.
活在当下
You are your now.
就是当下
And you are here in the now.
俗世消失
The world around you disappears.
自我便是穹宇
You are a universe unto yourself,
紧跟自我的节拍
in tune only with yourself.
做得好  Sabrina
Good, Sabrina.
很好  Nadya
Very nice, Nadya.
Rick？
Rick?
你眼睛是看Alison的PP呢
Should your eyes be on Alison's bum
还是闭上呢？
or should they be closed?
心无旁骛
There is no one else.
前无闲人
There is no one in front of you,
后无来者
no one behind you,
左无生灵
nobody to your left,
右亦如此
and nobody to the right.
太棒了  Noomi
Excellent, Noomi.
Namaste：巴斯克语  表示合十礼
谢谢  Dutta大师
Namaste, Guru Dutta.
真爱如血  第七季第三集
真爱字幕组出品
多久了？
How long?
Eric？
Eric?
你说什么？（再说一遍）
Can you repeat the question?
你病多久了？
How long have you been sick?
第一迹象是在上个月表现出的
Saw the first signs last month.
那就是在圣彼得堡
When you were in St. Petersburg.
别表现得那么惊讶
Don't act all surprised.
我他妈的满地球找你
I searched the whole fucking planet for you.
圣他妈的圣彼得堡  Eric
Saint fucking Petersburg, Eric?
你知道我有多讨厌俄国佬儿
You know how I hate the Russian people.
额  我不知道你会找我
Well, I didn't know you were gonna come looking for me.
对  那你干嘛还到处跑？
Yeah, then why'd you keep on moving?
恭喜你  Pam
Congratulations, Pam.
你赢了
You've outwitted me.
但也只是因为我不舒服
But only because I'm not well.
Tara不在了
Tara met the true death.
昨晚我在摩洛哥时感应到的
I felt it last night when I was in Morocco.
她是我的后裔  Eric
She was my progeny, Eric.
你不说点儿什么吗？
You're not gonna say anything?
你玩那个游戏了？
Did you play the bucket game?
玩了
I did.
哦
Oh.
我喜欢那游戏
I like the bucket game.
你到底怎么了？
What is wrong with you?
你他妈是Eric Northman
You are Eric fucking Northman.
你不能放弃  你得斗争
You don't give up. You fight.
斗争结束了  Pam
Fight's over, Pam.
不会都是因为Sylvie吧
This can't all be about Sylvie.
Godric  Nora
Godric, Nora...
对  还有Sylvie
and, yes, Sylvie, too.
恩？
你在看什么？
看你
为什么?
因为我情不自禁
就算试着不去看
那好吧
一九八六年  法国罗姆河谷
尝尝看
我不能
你知道的
你会想念吗? 葡萄酒？
你才是我想要的
不  我想的是你  Sylvie
那我父亲呢?
让他自撸吧
如果他发现我们的事
我就催眠让他忘记
或者杀了他
你想怎样都行
（法语）对！
Oui!
太好了  Northman先生
Bravo, Mr. Northman.
你他妈是谁？
Who the fuck are you?
Gainesborough大臣说你很高大
Chancellor Gainesborough said you were tall.
但你还是让我印象深刻
Yet somehow I'm still impressed.
你是当局的
You're Authority.
是谁？
她想要什么？
有地方谈谈吗？
Is there someplace we can talk?
未向当地治安官报道
Failure to register with your local sheriff,
未向当地治安官报税  未向…
failure to pay taxes to your local sheriff, failure--
我不喜欢你
I don't like you.
这不公平  De Beaufort小姐
That's not fair, Miss De Beaufort.
如果在别的情况下相见
Were the circumstances of our meeting different,
我相信你我会成为朋友的
I think you and I could've been friends.
看出来了  你穿多大鞋？
I can see it. What size shoe do you wear?
可能会成为朋友
Could have been friends.
但情况就是这样
Circumstances are what they are.
你们太坏了  小伙姑娘啊
You've been bad, boys and girls,
是时候归队了
and it is time to fall in line.
我们不能两者兼容
Because we can't have it both ways.
要么我们隐匿藏身
We're either living in hiding
要么就置身公众
or we are out in the open.
但我们公开咬人
But we can't very well remain hidden
还和那酒商的女儿乱搞的话
when we are publicly biting, fucking, and sucking
就不会藏匿的太好
the vintner's daughter.
哇哦  那我能说什么？ 月光下的feel倍儿爽
Well, what can I say? It feels better in the moonlight.
那就找个带窗的房间
Then get a room with a window
月光倾泻而入
and let the moon shine in.
你们一定听说过Yokonomo公司吧？
I take it you've both heard of the Yokonomo Corporation?
日本医药公司？
Japanese pharmaceuticals?
没错
Correct.
当局和Yokonomo公司
The Authority and Yokonomo Corp
已经联合开发  即将向市场推出
have joined forces in the development and bringing to market
人工合成真血饮品
of a synthetic human blood substitute drink.
听起来挺美味
Sounds delicious.
我尝过了  你说的对
I've tasted it, and you would be correct.
没有Sylvie  事儿也能办成
It's no Sylvie, but it gets the job done.
因为真血  主流即将成为现实
With Tru Blood, mainstreaming is going to become a reality.
那日子该多无聊啊  无聊的想自杀
And everyone lived bored and suicidally ever after.
别卖萌了
Stop being cute.
很多人或许喜欢你的微笑
Many might appreciate your smile,
但我向你保证  Yokonomo公司不会
but I can assure you, the Yokonomo Corporation will not.
那可是大生意  赚大钱
This is big business, big money,
他们绝不会接受拒绝
and they will not take no for an answer.
当局也是
Nor will the Authority.
我的任务就是确定你明白这点儿
It is my job to make sure you understand this.
我懂了
I understand.
- Eric? - Northman先生?
- Eric? - Mr. Northman?
滚你丫的
Go fuck yourself.
很好
Very well.
我会确保所有相关部门
I'll make sure all theinterested parties
都收到你的答复
are aware of your answer.
很荣幸见到你  Sylvie
甜心？
别担心
这女人是当局的  Eric
That woman was Authority, Eric,
你就只对她说个滚你丫的
and you just told her to go fuck herself.
我们今晚就得走了
We need to leave tonight.
我喜欢法国
I like France.
我们不走
We're not leaving.
苍天啊
Jesus Christ.
如果你想带她就带  但我们必须走
Bring her with if you have to, but let's go.
Sylvie想上完大学
Sylvie wants to finish university.
她想什么？
She wants to what?
她正在读艺术史
She's studying art history.
我和你一样钟爱法国女人  Eric
I am as big a fan of the French vagina as you are, Eric,
但你得醒醒
but come back to Earth.
她只是个人类
She's just a human.
我们在一起多久了  Pam？
We've been together how long now, Pam?
81年
81 years.
在这81年里
In those 81 years,
我们好好保护你吗？
have I ever failed to protect you?
不是
No--
你是我的后裔
You're my progeny.
你没必要和Flanagan小姐或者当局统一战线
You do not fall in line with Miss Flanagan or the Authority.
听我的就是了
You fall in line with me.
嘿  Sook？
Hey, Sook?
我饿了  晚餐吃什么？
I'm starving. What are you thinking for dinner?
嘿  冰箱里的牛排
Hey, those steaks in the freezer,
你认为那多久才能解冻？
how long you think it'll take 'em to thaw?
Sook？
Sook?
嘿？
Hey?
我擦
Shit.
该死  Sookie
God damn it, Sookie.
Bill！  Bill！
Bill! Bill!
我知道她来这儿了！
I know she came here!
我能闻到她的味道！
I can fuckin' smell her!
狼人是这世上最好的追踪者
Werewolves are the best trackers on the planet.
我掩盖了我们的行踪  Sookie
I covered our tracks, Sookie.
Alcide不会找到我们的
Alcide won't be finding us.
好  很好
Okay, good.
现在和你谈这个会不会太迟了？
Is it too late for me to talk you out of this?
你怎么感觉不到我了？
How come you can't feel me anymore?
我以为喝了你的血
I thought once I'd had your blood,
那便是永久
it was forever.
在集中营
At that camp
我喂养了所有的吸血鬼
where I fed all those vampires,
几乎被吸干  Sookie
I was completely drained, Sookie.
Jessica和James替我输血
Jessica and James may have saved my life
才救了我
by transfusing me,
如今的Bill Compton
but the Bill Compton that I am today
和你血液里流淌的Bill Compton
has nothing to do with the Bill Compton
已经没有任何关系了
whose blood flows through your veins.
所以你是说你脱胎换骨了？
So you're saying you get a clean slate, then?
你已不再是那个
That you're not the same vampire
对我做出恐怖行为的吸血鬼了？
who did all those horrible things to me?
不
No.
那些曾对你做过的事
I have to live with the memories
我会永远带着这些记忆活着
of what I'd done to you forever.
我不能除去任何罪责
I can't acquit myself of any of it.
很好
Good.
如果我们要完成这个计划
If we're gonna go through with this plan,
那你就得吸我的血
then you're gonna have to take my blood
要不我帮不了你
or I won't be able to help you.
我有男朋友
I have a boyfriend.
你觉得Rocky安全吗?
Do you think Rocky's okay?
恩  Wade  我确定
Yes, Wade, I do.
你希望我妈妈没事儿吗？
Do you think my mom's okay?
我真的这样期望
I really hope so.
你认为我们都能平安无事吗？
Do you think we're gonna be okay?
想知道个秘密吗？
Do you want to know a secret?
你和我…
You and me...
曾经有过一次
we made out once.
我会  我会记得这些的
I would-- I would remember something like that.
不  我说真的  有吸血鬼
No, really. A vampire
对你迷魂了  但确有其事  我发誓
glamoured it outta you, but we did, I swear.
真的吗？  我们曾经做过？
Really? We really made out?
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
这是这段儿我听到最好的消息了
This is the best news I've heard in a while.
Adilyn！
Adilyn!
- Jessica! - 老爸来了  宝贝儿！
- Jessica! - Andy: Daddy's coming, baby!
- 你们一起来了？ - 恩
- You guys came together? - Yeah.
别告诉他我们刚…
Don't tell him that we were just about to--
- 别担心  我不会的  - 恩
- Don't worry, I won't. - Okay.
- 谁对你做的这些？ - 我们试着阻止他们
- Who did this to you? - We tried to stop 'em,
但他们拿走了所有的枪支弹药
but they took all your guns, all your ammo,
一切东西
everything.
- 谁做的？  - 我不知道  都有
- Who did? - I don't know, everyone.
整个镇子  就连Rocky也是其中一员
The whole town. Even Rocky was part of it.
别让他惹上麻烦
Don't get him in trouble.
孩子  我们都有麻烦了
Son, we're all in trouble.
等等  他们去找谁了？
Wait, who are they after?
他们去找每一个
They're after anyone and anything
和他们不一样的人或物
that's different than they are.
- 恩哼  - 你用最简单的
- Uh-huh. - You take the simplest,
每天你都会做的事
most everyday thing you do...
这些人…这些人曾只是
These people-- these people were just
坐下来等着吃个披萨夜宴
sitting down for a frozen pizza dinner.
假如那是你生命里
What if that was the last thing
最后一件事情呢？
you were ever gonna do?
因为生活不会是只吃一半披萨
'Cause life is supposed to add up to something,
它是事情叠叠加加
not be some half-eaten slice of pizza.
他们抓走了我的未婚妻  牧师
And they got my fiance, Reverend.
我知道
I know they do, Sam.
你们掳走了我的未婚妻和未出世的孩子
They got my fiance and my unborn child,
我的人生才刚刚加入新元素啊
and my life is just startin' to add up to something,
我不能…
and I can't--
现在你…你要救他们回来
Now you-- you're gonna get 'em back.
你会见到你的孩子
You're gonna meet that baby of yours,
但你得有信心（也指信仰）
but you've got to have faith.
牧师  他们到处都是耶稣啊
Reverend, they had Jesuses everywhere.
墙上也是
They had Jesuses on the walls,
每间卧室的壁炉架上都画耶稣
they had Jesuses on the mantel in every single bedroom.
他们有信仰
They had faith.
那又有什么用？
What good did it do 'em?
那到底又有什么用啊？
What good would not having had it done them?
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
至少他们不会对死亡将至的现实
At least they wouldn't have been blind to the fact
充耳不闻
that death was coming.
看看现在  我可不会在众人面前
Now looky here, this ain't the kind of thing
说这些事儿的
I say in front of a congregation,
但这会儿就你和我
but since it's just you and me right now,
死亡…那…
death-- whew--
那个暗黑的混帐东西
is a dark and blinding motherfucker,
不管你看不看得见他的到来
whether you see it coming or you don't.
人生都荒废在迎它的路上了
But a life spent in anticipation of it coming,
Sam  好吧  那不是该有的人生
Sam, well, that's not a life worth living.
Daniel牧师  抱歉打扰你
Reverend Daniels, I am so sorry to interrupt you,
- 但是她又发狂了  - Tara！Tara！
- but she is freaking out again. - Tara! Tara!
你都做了什么 Willa？
What'd you do, Willa?
又给了她点儿血
I gave her more blood.
Tara  你去哪儿？
Tara, where'd you go?
告诉妈妈你在哪儿！
Tell Mama where you at!
Lettie Mae! Lettie Mae!
- 你不是Tara！ - 我知道  亲爱的
- You ain't Tara! - I know, honey.
她受伤了
She was hurt.
我不知道还能做什么  对不起
I didn't know what else to do. I'm sorry.
好吧  镇长先生  很抱歉
All right, Mr. Mayor, I'm sorry,
我能请你们都离开吗？
but could I ask you all to leave?
拜托了  请离开吧  谢谢你们
Please, please leave. Thank you.
好  冷静点儿  看着我
Okay, now calm down. Look at me.
听我说  现在  我们…
Listen to me. Now, what did we--
- Tara！ - 不  不！
- Tara! - No, no!
- 冷静点  嘘 - Tara Tara
- Hold on. Shh. - Tara, Tara.
- Lettie Mae 有我呢  - Tara
- Lettie Mae, stay with me. - Tara.
额  真尴尬
Well, that was awkward.
恩  确实
Yeah, it was.
牧师有的忙了
The Reverend's got his hands full.
- Matt？ - 怎么  镇长先生？
- Matt? - Yes, Mr. Mayor?
你可真是吸血鬼的菜啊  不是吗？
You're awful dishy for a vampire, aren't you?
就聊聊天嘛
Just trying to make conversation.
哇噢 这他妈又演哪儿出？
Well, ain't this fucking perfect?
你们都在这儿干什么？
What are y'all doing out here?
夺回小镇
Taking our town back.
就你们  恩？
You are, huh?
确实
Indeed.
对
Yeah.
- 你告诉他们了？ - 没错他说了
- You told 'em? - Damn right he told us.
我就知道你有问题
I knew there was something off about you.
现在终于明白了
Now I know what it is.
你是警察 Kenya  我是你的镇长
You're a cop, Kenya. I'm your mayor.
就是说  你是黑人  他是白人
Translation-- you black, he's white.
哦  我懂了  姑娘
Oh, I got it, girl.
嘿  Rocky  你听我说
Hey, Rocky, you listen to me.
你想救你妈妈回来吗  那就过来
You want to get your mom back, you come with me
因为这样救不了她
'cause this ain't helpin' her.
当然能  我们有枪
Sure, it is. We got guns.
你想赌赌谁才安全吗  恩？
How much you wanna bet who's safer, huh?
我们的枪能干掉那些吸血鬼
Our guns against your fag vampire.
嘿  你是…
Hey, who you-- -
该死的  Vince！
God damn it, Vince!
- 对  我们才安全  没错  - 对
Yeah, we're safer, all right. - Man: Yep.
不  Merlotte镇长  去你丫的
No, Mayor Merlotte, God damn you.
你欺骗了良辰镇的善男信女
You tricked the fine men and women of Bon Temps
让他们以为投选出一个人类
into thinking they were voting for a human being
而真相却是他们选出来的是个恶魔
when the truth is they were voting for the Devil.
你说啊  Gibson镇长
You tell him, Mayor Gibson.
人民有发言权
The people have spoken.
我现在才是镇长
I'm the mayor now.
作为镇长  我建议你现在回家
And as mayor, I'm advising you to go on home,
或者  离开良辰镇更好
or better yet, leave Bon Temps for good.
好  那抱歉了  各位
Well, I'm sorry, y'all,
但我属于这儿
but I belong here.
- 杀了它！ - 知道！
- Kill it! - Man: Get it!
知道吗  我想过的
You know, I've been thinking.
如果我们熬过这关
If we ever make it through this,
你会考虑
would you ever consider
和我要个孩子吗？
maybe having a baby with me?
你他妈在开玩笑吗？
Are you fucking kidding me?
我知道你不行  但我们可以领养
I know you can't make babies, but we could adopt.
我就是觉得  经过这一切
I just feel, with everything going on...
没家的男人一无是处
a man ain't nothing without a family.
怎么？
What?
一个遍布死人的小镇
One town of dead people
怎么就把你变成一个娘炮了？
and you're gonna let it turn you into a girl?
我  娘炮？
Me, a girl?
在我的年代  一个男人
In my day, when men marched to a village
走进一个被焚毁的小镇
that was burned to the ground
目睹妇孺被烧焦的遗骸
and bore witness to the charred remains
战争将他们抛掷脑后
of women and children that war leaves in its wake,
你认为他们还会多想吗？
do you think they gave it a second thought?
他们不会
They didn't.
他们什么都不想  也不会感知其他
They didn't think anything. They didn't feel anything.
因为那时  男人都是战士
Because back then, men were warriors.
嗯哼  好吧  我不想告诉你  Violet
Mm-hmm. Well, I hate to break it to you, Violet,
但我是现代男性
but I'm a modern man.
我会想  会感知
I think and I feel.
我他妈还依旧是个战士
And I'm still a badass motherfucker of a warrior.
我遇见你时
You were when I met you.
那天他们将你丢进我牢里
That day when they threw you into my cell,
当然  你是有点身心疲废
sure, you were a little broken.
但我还是很直白的说你是个男人
But I could tell right away that you were a man
就像从前的人
like they used to make them,
有原则的活着
who lived by a code.
有荣誉  有尊严的人
Who had a sense of honor and dignity
如铁铸般锻造
and an iron-forged cock.
这才是我爱的男人
That's the man I fell for.
草你妹的现代人
Fuck being modern.
- Jason?  - Stackhouse!
Jason? - Andy: Stackhouse!
我和Jason正在打嘴架
Jason and I are in the middle of a fight,
所以你丫识相滚开
so fuck off.
Stackhouse  我们有麻烦了
Stackhouse, we got a problem.
能进来吗？
Can we come in?
恩  进来吧
Yeah, come on in.
嘿  发生什么了？
Hey, what's going on?
不准再向前  懂吗？
Not one step further, got that?
这是我的房子
This is my house.
Vince和他的同党
Vince and all his yahoos
冲进警局  偷走了所有枪支
broke into the station, stole all our guns.
他们怎么说服Kenya的？
How'd they get past Kenya?
Kenya也是其中一员
Kenya's one of 'em.
哦  该死
Oh, shit.
是你来告诉他  还是我来？
Do you wanna tell him or should I?
告诉我什么？
Tell me what?
说啊
What?
Adilyn担心他们在找Sookie
Adilyn's afraid that they might be after Sookie.
别担心  Stackhouse
Don't worry, Stackhouse.
我们不会让她有事的
We ain't gonna let nothing happen to her.
我能让Adilyn和Wade躲在这里
It all right if I let Adilyn and Wade
随后再来接他们吗？
hole up here till I can come back for 'em?
恩  当然
Yeah, sure.
别出去
Do not go outside.
别给任何人开门
Do not open the door for anyone.
我可不在附近
I'm not fucking around.
她不会听我的
She won't listen to me,
但是  Wade  你得听话
but, Wade, you better.
我们这样说定了
I'll make you a deal.
我们在找到Sookie前休战怎么样？
How about we call a truce until we find Sookie?
好  可以
Okay, fine.
但我不认为我们之间有什么问题
But I didn't realize that we still had a problem.
这种盲目乐观的态度只会让我讨厌你
It's "Pollyanna" Shit like that that makes me hate you.
好了  各位  出发吧
All right, y'all, let's do this.
爆他丫的
Fuckin' A.
干嘛？
Yeah?
我靠…
Get the fuck--
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
怎么了  夕阳西下了？
What's wrong, Sundown?
你不喜欢我煮的菜吗？
Don't you like what I was cooking?
还有大麻吗？
Got any more of that weed?
木  没有了
Nope, no more weed.
昨晚都抽光了
Smoked me clean out last night.
但如果你一起
But I'll bust out the pharmacy
我会去药房买
if you wanna join.
希望可以  但吸血鬼不能吞药
I wish I could, but vampires can't swallow pills.
好吧  见鬼
Well, damn.
永生也并没标榜的那么好
Immortality's not all it's cracked up to be.
恩啊
Hmm.
我来问你
Let me ask you something.
现在  我知道我在逃避什么
Now, I know what I was escaping from,
但你心里在逃避什么呢？
but what's on your mind that you want off?
我猜  就Jessica的烂事儿
Just Jessica shit, I guess.
关于Jessica的哪种事情呢?
Any particular kind of Jessica shit?
可以长篇大论的那种
There's a longer version of this conversation,
但我没那心情
but I'm not really in the mood.
简而言之的呢
The shorter version goes something like--
我们住一起  睡在彼此身边
we live together, we sleep next to each other,
时而来一炮
occasionally we fuck,
但我不确定她是否真的走心了
but I'm not so sure she even knows I'm there.
恩啊
Mm.
或许她才是漫不经心的那个
Maybe she's the one who ain't there.
- 恩  也许  - 大概
- Hmm, maybe. - Maybe.
但是长篇大论的话
But that's the longer version.
记得你上次吞的什么药吗？
'Member what it was, the last pill you took?
吐诺尔（镇静剂或催眠药，商标名）
- Tuinal. - Tuinal?
- 嗯哼  - 恩
- Mm-hmm. - Mm.
我可没机会尝试  感觉如何？
I never had the chance. How was it?
哦  它仿佛让你置身海洋
Oh, it turns your body into an ocean.
海洋啊
Ocean.
让你的意识乘风逐浪
And lets your consciousness ride that wave.
哦  我要来吞一颗吐诺尔
Ooh, I'm gonna make me a Tuinal.
- 你又不能吞  - 当然  你能
- You can't make a Tuinal. - Sure, you can.
古今药物都是一个样儿
Today's drugs are just like drugs back in your day.
只不过现在被解构了
Except they've been deconstructed.
化整为散  支离凌乱
They separate out the parts of the whole into pieces.
现在他们这么命名
Now they call them this,
那么称呼  随它吧
that, or whatever.
而我只用拿这个
And all I gotta do is take this,
选那个  无所谓
that, or whatever
然后整一起
and put it together.
在你知道前
And before you know it,
就可以通过吐诺尔随浪逐波了
you're gonna be riding that Tuinal wave
就像是回到你所喜爱的童年时光
just like you did back in your love child days.
如我所说  我不能再吞药了
Like I said, I can't swallow pills anymore.
那我来
I'll do the swallowing.
给我20分钟
Just give 'em 20 minutes
让它们融入我的血管
to get to know each other in my bloodstream,
我就能带你漫步海滩
then I'm gonna take you to the beach.
我们下边还有多少？
How many more we got left down there?
四个人
Four.
你把那个孕妇当一个还是两个？
Are you counting the pregnant lady as one or two?
加上孩子  就五个
Counting the baby, we've got five.
我数学烂透了  那这是几天的食物？
I'm shit at math. How many more days of food is that?
拜你所赐  最多两天
Two max, thanks to you.
听着  我们还得再回去一次
Look, we're just gonna have to go back out there again.
什么？不  我不去
What? No, I can't.
我没那个精力了
I don't have the energy.
你以为我有吗？  我们没得选
You think I do? We ain't got no choice.
他们有吸血鬼保护着  真的
They've got vampires protecting them, they do.
我们都知道
And we know that now.
我们要带着银链  木桩
We'll bring silver chains, stakes.
不会有事的
It'll be all right.
我每隔一小时都得吃东西
I have to eat every hour on the hour.
假如我们出去
What happens if we go out there
却没有找到任何人呢?
and we don't find anybody?
那就带一个和我们一起去捕猎
We'll bring one of them out there hunting with us, then.
什么  像旅行食品袋？
What, like trail mix?
灵魂驻守者
Spirits who watch over us,
亲朋  好友  先祖  门神
family, friends, ancestors, guardians of the gate,
我们召唤你
we call thee forth.
以此仪式  虔诚召唤
With this rite, we evoke you.
- 灵魂驻守者  - 这他妈在干吗？
- Spirits who watch over us - The fuck's this?
哦  该死
Oh, shit.
你们谁觉得她是哈利波特啊？
Now, which one of you thinks she's Harry Potter?
- 我说是谁？ - 我  是我
- I said which one? - Me. It's me.
Holly  不
Holly, no.
我开的头  没事儿  我没事儿
I started it-- it's okay, I'm okay.
想和我们一起狩猎吗  哈利？
You in the mood to go hunting with us, Harry?
Alcide会同意的  你知道的
Alcide would be right, you know.
- 什么？ - 你的计划
- What about? - This plan of yours.
不是最好的
It's shaky at best.
如果你要更好的  我洗耳恭听
I'm all ears, if you got a better one.
你知道  我这计划有一半算是你的
You know, this plan of mine is half yours.
- 你的主意  - 我才没有
- You gave me the idea. - I did no such thing.
有  你当然有
Sure, you did.
你第一次带我去Fangtasia
The first time you took me to Fangtasia,
去的路上  在车上
in the car on the way there
你说我是吸血鬼诱饵
you called me "Vampire bait."
那不是女孩能忘记的事情
That's not something a girl forgets.
我不是那意思
I didn't mean it literally.
我知道你没有  但当我们商议时
I know you didn't, but when we say stuff,
我们无法决定人们如何上钩
we can't decide how people are gonna take it.
我今晚所做的
All I'm doing tonight
就是要完成我的目的
is fulfilling my purpose.
我们就期待坏人上钩吧
Let's just hope the bad guys take the bait.
假如一切按计行事
If everything goes as planned
他们会带你去其他人的关押之地
and they take you to where they're holding the others,
当我去找你时
you want me to bring Alcide along
要我带着Alcide一起吗？
when I come and find you?
天  恩  带上Alcide
Hell, yeah, bring Alcide.
带任何愿意帮忙的人来
Bring anybody who's willing to help.
我们可有不少人需要救助
There's a whole lot of us that are gonna need rescuing.
至少…我希望有
A-- at least I hope there are,
我最不需要的就是
and the last thing I need
再有他人因我而死
is anybody else dying 'cause of me.
你爱他？
You love him?
这不关你的事儿  William Compton
That would be none of your business, William Compton.
如果我们还是朋友  Sookie
If we're to be friends, Sookie,
我们就应该谈点儿这种事儿
we should be able to talk about things like this.
他想要孩子
He wants kids.
你不想吗?
Ain't that what you want?
当你我在一起时  孩子就像…
When you and I were together, children was something--
我确实爱他  Bill
I do love him, Bill.
真的
I really do.
但在内心深处
But there's something
有些事…
deep down and...
就算是对自己
I've never said this before,
之前我也从未想过
even to myself.
我怕我对他的爱
I'm afraid that I don't love him
没有他对我那么深
as much as he loves me.
我知道我应该如此
And I know I should
因为Alcide他
because Alcide is decent
英俊  靠谱
and handsome and grounded
是个好人  知道吗？
and he's good, you know?
当我们彼此倾诉“我爱你”时
But when we tell each other "I love you"...
我能从他的声音里
I can hear it in his voice
思想里看出来
and I can hear it in his thoughts.
他确实比我爱的深
He means it more than I do.
我知道  那让我觉得
I know it, and it makes me feel
在由内而外的崩坏
so effin' rotten inside,
我不知道自己还能撑多久
I don't know how much longer I can take it.
爱不是永远平等的  Sookie
Love isn't always equal, Sookie.
或许你会更爱他
Maybe you'll grow to love him more.
也许吧
Maybe.
我也会理解他对我的爱少一点
I'd take him lovin' me a little less just the same.
嘿  我是Sookie
Hey, this is Sookie.
我现在没空  请留言
I'm not in right now. Please leave a message.
没错  操蛋的嘟声  Sookie  又是我
Yeah, beep fucking beep. Sook, it's me again.
听着  我们来你家
Listen, we went over to your house
门大开着  屋里也没人
and the door was open and no one was home.
现在  我真的开始担心了
Now I'm really starting to worry,
所以拜托你听到后  给我回电好吗？
so when you get this, would you please call me?
- 我们有麻烦了  - 那是Sam的皮卡吗？
- We got trouble. - Isn't that Sam's truck?
Sook  我得挂了  回电
Sook, I gotta go. Call me.
- 在这边  - 注意了
- Over here. - Heads up.
过来  来
Come on, move.
晚上好啊  警长
Evening, Sheriff.
还有副将
Deputy.
我说  镇长在哪儿？
Where's the mayor, y'all?
- 他飞走了  - 对  我们看到了
- He flew away. - Man: Yeah. We saw it.
能帮你做些什么？
What can do ya for?
恩  除非你能放了警长的女儿
Well, unless you can un-lock up the sheriff's daughter,
还有把偷走的枪还回来
and unless you can un-steal our guns,
除了别他妈的挡道儿
then you can do us for shit
或是让我们拿你来练枪
except for get the fuck outta our way
那你就能拍拍狗腿了事儿了
or let us take target practice on you.
他说什么？
What did he say?
会是怎样呢？
Which one's it gonna be?
你女儿用手上发出的什么光击中我
Your daughter struck me with lightning that shot out her hands.
我知道  听说了  我很为她骄傲
I know, I heard, and I'm very proud of her.
现在  是让我们过去还是怎样？
Now, y'all gonna let us through or what?
你说呢  Vince？
What do you say, Vince?
原地不动
Hold your ground.
我受够了
Enough of this shit.
Stackhouse和红头发是我的
Stackhouse and Red are mine.
Fortenberry夫人  我真不建议那样
Mrs. Fortenberry, I do not recommend that.
- 我可是在你家长大的  - 闭嘴 你俩
- I grew up in your house. - Shut up, the both of you.
你们让Hoyt离我而去
You made Hoyt leave me.
把他从妈妈身边逼走
You drove him away from his mama.
那是分手  人们都会分别
It was a breakup. People break up.
放屁  你伤碎了他的心
Bullshit. You tore out his heart
还不当回事儿
like he didn't even matter.
他很重要
He mattered.
该死
Shit!
Rocky!
你会害死自己的
You're gonna get yourself killed out there.
Rocky!
要我替你去抓他吗?
You want me to go get him for you?
- 要活的  - 我知道
- Alive. - I know.
啊！
Ah!
嘿  你为什么不能愈合？
Hey, how come you ain't healin'?
我不知道
I don't know.
你安全了  脑残
You're safe, shithead.
安全？  你他妈才是敌人
Safe? You're the fucking enemy.
哦  是吗？  你确定？
Oh, yeah? You sure about that?
走！
Come on!
食物
Food.
待着  别说话
Stay here. Say nothing.
Troy  你和Mark带这俩回去
Troy, you and Mark take these two back to the others.
- 会的  朋友  - 不  拜托
- Will do, mate. - No, please.
闭嘴  女士  坏事儿总在发生
Fuck off, lady. Shit happens.
我们走
Let's go.
哦  听到低音了吗？
Oh, you feel that bass?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
低音  伙计  哦  那是Norco  低音？
Bass, man. Oh, you feel He's the Norco. Bass?
变换舞台  他们在海洋上演奏
Turn the stage, they playin' on into ocean.
哦  还有鼓声  是Ativan
Oh, and the drums. That's the Ativan.
没错  听好了
Exactly. Listen to 'em now.
水流不断
Makin' the water all choppy.
- 号角声来了  - 号角声
- Here come the horns. - The horns.
是的  先生  号角声
Yes, sir, the horns.
号角声是Molly   Molly用来加速
The horns is Molly, Molly gathering speed.
Molly激起音浪
Molly making waves.
操蛋的过往啊
Fuck the past.
特别是当你不知道是否有未来时
Especially since you don't know if you've got a future.
一切
Everything.
我们抛下的一切都毫无用处
Everything behind us is fucking useless.
- 恩  - 一切
- Mm. - Everything.
现在才是最重要的
Now is all that matters.
吐诺尔  小妖精
Tuinal, bitch.
- 没错  - 吐诺尔
- Yeah. - Tuinal.
Alcide  你在外边干吗？
Alcide, what are you doing out?
Sookie失踪了  我在Bill房子那里跟丢了
Sookie's missing. I lost her scent at Bill's house.
开枪啊  懦夫
Take the shot, you pussy.
我才不是懦夫  枪卡了
I ain't no pussy. Gun's jammed.
该死！
Shit!
他们到底在哪儿？
Where the hell are they?
要不是我很了解
If I didn't know better,
我会说你这都是咎由自取
I would say that you were looking forward to this.
只是他们不肯上钩
It's just them not taking the bait
让人有点泄气而已
is a little insulting, is all.
我以为我的气味很特别
I thought I smelled special.
哦  确实
Oh, you do.
六旗：世界上最大的过山车主题公园
你有去过六旗吗?
Have you ever been to Six Flags?
我不能说有那种荣幸
I cannot say that I've had the pleasure.
那不是关闭了吗?
Didn't they close that down?
大概是在五六年前吧
Like, five or six years ago, I think it was.
但我爷爷曾经在我九岁生日那天
But my grandpa took me and Jason there once
带我跟Jason去过
for my ninth birthday.
总之  他们有种像是自由落体的东西
Anyway, they had this ride, like a free-fall thing,
你知道的  就是把你关在笼子里
you know, where they put you in this cage
然后将你推出高台
and then they push you out over this ledge
抛向空中几百尺高
hundreds of feet up in the sky.
你那时九岁?
You were nine?
我是说  虽然我是不朽的  但那也把我给吓死了
I mean, I'm immortal and that would scare me to death.
下落还不是最糟的
The fall wasn't the worst part.
而是置空时
It was the waiting.
你知道它们会把你抛下去
You knew they were gonna drop you,
只是不知道是什么时候
you just didn't know when.
这确实是切身感受
That's exactly what this feels like.
你应该上战场试试
You should try going to war.
这是战争吗  Bill？
Is this war, Bill?
是
Yeah.
没错  我想是
Yeah, I suppose it is.
嘘  嘘
Shh. Shh.
我不想这样做
I don't wanna do this.
这是为你父亲的  Sarah
It's for your father, Sarah.
这样他可以走时  有张照片作为留念
So he has a picture to remember us by while he's away.
过来
Come here.
你害怕吗？
Are you frightened?
是的  父亲
Yes, Father.
怕什么？  相机吗？
What of, the camera?
- 不  - 那  是什么？
- No. - Well, what, then?
你必须走吗？
Do you have to go?
亲爱的  我们说过的
Darlin', we discussed this.
那你会回来吗？
Are you going to come home?
是  当然会  亲爱的
Yes, of course I am, darlin'.
那你为什么还需要一张照片？
Then why do you need the photograph?
这样…
So...
当我想你们的时候  我就可以看到你
I can look at you and your mother and your brother
你妈妈  还有弟弟
when I'm feeling lonesome for ya.
- 这不一样  - 对  是不一样
- It won't be the same. - No, it won't.
但比见不到你们好多了啊
But it'll be a lot better than not being able to see you at all.
下一个？
Next?
我有主意了
I have an idea.
- 请问您贵姓？ - Fortenberry 先生
- May I ask your name? - Fortenberry, sir.
我是Julian Fortenberry
Julian Fortenberry.
Fortenberry先生  请问
Mr. Fortenberry, might I ask whether
能否先拍张我和我女儿的合影
you would photograph myself and my daughter first,
然后再拍全家福呢？
and then we can do the rest of my family after?
额  你也看到了  我这儿锡料不多
Well, I have only so many tins, you see,
而且它们很贵
and they're quite expensive.
恩  很乐意支付费用
Well, I will gladly pay the cost.
拜托了  求你了
Please, I beg you.
恩  我想这也没什么大不了
Well, I suppose there's no harm in it.
- 这边请  先生  - 谢谢你  先生
- Right this way, sir. - Thank you, sir.
请您坐在那张椅子上
If you'd just take your mark on that chair right there, please.
现在  保持姿势不动
Now, we'll need to be very still.
这是给你留念
This one's for you to keep.
三 二 一  别动
In three, two, one, freeze.
真有爱  现在是妈妈和宝宝
Lovely. And now mother and baby.
你要我…
You would like me...
就坐在那张椅子上
In that chair right there
那就太好了  谢谢你  贵姓…
would be wonderful, thank you, Mrs., uh...
Compton
Compton.
真是个有爱的家庭  Compton先生
You have a beautiful family, Mr. Compton.
谢谢你  先生
Thank you, sir.
现在  保持姿势
Now, very still.
三 二 一  别动
In three, two, one, freeze.
Sookie
Sookie...
我等够了
I'm sick of waiting.
来啊  你们
Come on, y'all!
我尝起来阳光与花香同在
I taste like sunshine and flowers
我他妈的就在这里！
and I'm right fuckin' here!
她睡着了吗?
Is she asleep?
终于  是的
Finally, yes.
之前真对不起
I'm so sorry about before.
这不是你的错  Willa
It ain't your fault, Willa.
你真认为她是有意烫伤自己的吗?
Do you really think she burned herself on purpose?
上帝造我们的时候  Willa
When the good Lord made us, Willa,
让我们万事皆有因
He gave us reflexes for a reason.
就连水都知道烧滚时要沸腾
Even water knows to jump off a griddle when it's hot.
- 你饿了吗? - 我能挨到明天
- You hungry? - I can wait until tomorrow.
不不不  甜心  不  不
No, no, no, sweetheart. No, no.
来吧  靠过来
Go on, scoot over.
你确定?  你是牧师
Are you sure? You're a reverend.
我确定
I'm sure.
啊
Ah.
就在我一生最糟的事后
I moved to this town
我搬到了这个小镇
after the worst period of my life.
我和我的第一任妻子
My first wife and I had--
失去了最年幼的女儿
we had lost our youngest daughter
那持续了六个月
going on six months before,
而那…
and it had--
毁了我们
it destroyed us.
我的妻子Tanya  她…
My wife Tanya, well...
误入迷途
she strayed.
而我…
And I...
失去信仰
I lost all faith...
对上帝  对众生  还有我的婚姻
in God, people, in my marriage...
以及自我
and in myself.
邻居和会众
Neighbors and congregates,
他们带着拌菜或派
they'd come by
前来会访
with casseroles or pies
或只是要想看看我的情况
or just to check up on me.
但你看  我会假装自己不在
But you see, I would pretend I wasn't there.
我会拉起窗帘  关掉电视
I'd have the curtains drawn and the television off.
躲在屋角
I'd be cowering in a corner...
试着屏住呼吸  害怕有人
trying to hold my breath for fear that someone
和我说话
would talk to me.
跌入低谷
I was low.
而后一日清晨  醒来扣好衣领
And then one morning, I woke up, put on my collar,
上了车后  就开车
I got in the car, and I started driving.
不知道该去哪
Had no idea where to
直到我停在这个用木条封起的教堂
until I pulled up to this boarded-up church.
相邻的那间教堂
This church right next door.
而屋外的阶梯上站着
And on the front steps was this
这美丽的女人
beautiful woman
手握一瓶摩根船长威士忌
clutching onto a bottle of Captain Morgan,
她说  你是牧师吗?
and she said, "You the reverend?"
我说  是的我是
And I said, "I am a reverend."
她又说  我一直在等你
And she said, "I've been waiting on you."
现在  镇上的人们
Now, folks in this town,
他们都说是我救了Lettie Mae
they say I saved Lettie Mae Thornton,
说没有我  她不可能活
that without me, she wouldn't be alive.
但似乎没人理解
But what no one seems to understand
是那个女人救了我
is that that woman saved me
正如我救了她一样
every bit as much as I saved her.
你好了吗？
You done?
抱歉
Sorry.
你没必要道歉的
You have nothing to apologize for,
所以别再道歉了
so stop apologizing.
好
Okay.
你注意到屋里没有酒精饮料吗
You notice there's no liquor in this house.
恩
Yes.
那是因为我妻子是个好人
That's because my wife is a good person,
真的是个好人
a deeply good person.
但她得了一种疾病
But she's got a disease.
一种没有区别的疾病
It's a disease that don't discriminate.
就像是老鼠  什么都吃
It's like a rat. It'll eat whatever--
酒精  药片  赌博  性交…
booze, pills, gambling, sex...
或是V血
or vampire blood.
你是个好女孩  Willa
You're a nice girl, Willa.
我在那本书中了解了你所有的过往
And I read about all what you've been through in that book there.
为此我感到非常遗憾
And I am so very sorry for it.
但对于Lettie Mae  你现在所见的
But to Lettie Mae, all you look like now
就像喝了那瓶威士忌
is a bottle of Captain Morgan.
我不能再让你待在这了
I can't have you around here no more.
她骗过你一次  就会再来一次
She manipulated you once and she'll do it again.
好吧  我了解
Okay, I understand.
那谁保护你们呢？
Who's gonna protect you?
上帝会的  亲爱的  一如既往
God will, darlin'. Just like He always has.
祝你好运
Good luck.
谢谢你  Willa Burrell
Thank you, Willa Burrell,
谢谢你所做的一切
for everything you've done.
但我收回对你的邀请
But I rescind your invitation from this house.
嘿  伙计
Hey, man.
Lafayette?
Lafayette  拜托
Lafayette, come on.
Lafayette  拜托  醒醒  老兄
Lafayette, come on. Wake up, man.
Lafayette  醒醒
Lafayette, wake up.
你到底哪根筋不对啊？
What the hell is your malfunction?
- 我以为你因为我嗑多了  - 怎么会
- I thought you OD'd on me. - Never.
我说过的  我是专家
I told you, I is a professional.
看看你
Look at you.
你担心我？
You worried about me?
我在你心里生根发芽了？
Am I growing on you?
哦  得了吧
Oh, shut up.
- 真可爱  - 别逗了
- It's cute. - Stop.
就是嘛
It is.
让我治好你的脖子  然后我就得走了
Let me fix your neck, and then I have to go.
好吧  我不动
Okay, I'm stopping.
- 你…  - 怎么？
- Is you-- - What?
要开发我吗?
Grooving on me?
听着  我 额
Look, I, um--
抱歉  我肯定是误解你之类的
I'm sorry. I must've misread you or something.
不  你并没有误解什么
No, you didn't misread anything.
只是…
It's just...
你知道的  我和Jessica在一起
you know, I'm with Jessica.
对
All right.
我懂
I gets it.
晚安
Good night.
好眠  亲爱的
Nighty-night, lover.
Eric?
我了个大去啊  Pam！
Jesus fucking Christ, Pam!
怎么了？
Now what?
我不会说  Northman先生
I wouldn't, Mr. Northman.
你远比自己所想的寡不敌众
You're more outnumbered than you are aware.
你叫什么  姑娘？
What's your name, girl?
Eric  我不懂
一切都不会有事的
就是个威胁  仅此而已
如果他们要杀了我们
早动手了
告诉他你的名字
Sylvie
Sylvie.
恩  Sylvie
Mm, Sylvie.
相当漂亮
So very pretty.
拿下她
Northman先生
Man: Mr. Northman.
Eric!
谁派你来的？
Who sent you?
我们是代表Yokonomo公司
We are here at the Yokonomo Corporation's behest.
那么  好  告诉他们说我懂了
Well, then, tell them I understand.
他们要表达的也表达了
They've made their point.
我未来会更加谨慎的  我保证
I will be more careful in the future, I promise.
你得做个选择  Northman先生
You have a choice to make, Mr. Northman.
其中一人非死不可
One of them has to die.
你来选
You pick.
- 动手吧  - 不
- Do it  - No.
停  停！
Stop, stop!
Eric!
好吧  你们想怎样？
Okay, what do you want?
钱？  我有钱
Money? I got money.
他们付你多少  我都双倍奉上
What are they paying you? I'll double it.
三倍也行
I will triple it for you.
你是个富裕的人
You're a wealthy man,
但你却不是公司
but you are no corporation.
选吧
Choose.
我很抱歉  Eric
I'm so sorry, Eric.
我
Me.
不
No.
杀了我
Kill me.
我恐怕  当局希望你活着
The Authority wants you alive, I'm afraid.
Pam
Pam.
放了Pam
Pam lives.
我们走
天就快亮了
你是故意接触病毒的吗?
Did you contract the virus on purpose?
故意  不是
On purpose, no.
难道我还要用
But did I go about my dealings
鬼在乎的态度来过日子？
with a devil-may-care attitude?
当然不
Absolutely.
你不能放弃  Eric
You can't give up, Eric.
现在有充足的血液供给
With an ample blood supply,
得病的吸血鬼能活得更久
vampires are living longer and longer with this disease.
谁知道他们是否在研发解药
And who knows, they're working on a cure.
他们很快就会研发了
They could have one soon.
求你了
Please.
我会帮你维持  直到…
I will help keep you well until--
为什么？
Why?
你真的后悔那晚你的选择吗？
Do you regret the choice you made that night?
我做了唯一能做的选择
I made the only choice I could.
那就别逼我目睹
Then don't make me watch this.
- 别逼我目睹  - 我早就放你走了
- Don't make me watch - I released you some time ago.
像你目睹Godric…
as you had to watch Godric...
- 目睹Nora… - 你该走了
- ...as you had to watch Nora. - You're free to leave.
别这样对我
Do not do this to me.
该死的
God damn you.
千余年来  世界如我口中蚌肉
For more than 1,000 years, the world has been my oyster.
如今也是
And it still can be.
我愿做任何事
I'll do anything.
我已失去一切喜好  Pam
I've lost my taste for oysters, Pam.
不
No.
你该走了
You should go.
Sarah Newlin
Sarah Newlin.
她怎么了？
What about her?
如果我告诉你Jason Stackhouse放了她呢？
What if I told you Jason Stackhouse let her live?
- 他没有  - 他有
- He didn't. - He did.
她就在外面
And she's out there.
- 哪里？ - 没人见过她
- Where? - No one's seen her.
我想她是躲起来了
I have to imagine she's in hiding somewhere.
哇噢  那我们就去找到她
Well, let's go find her.
可以吗？
Shall we?
屏住呼吸  Noomi
Hold your breath with me, Noomi.
我们要气息一致  一起极乐
We breathe together, we climax together.
（合十礼）太棒了
Namaste.
哦  Noomi  Noomi  Noomi
Oh, Noomi, Noomi, Noomi.
Sanbir啊  Sanbir啊  Sanbir啊
Sanbir, Sanbir, Sanbir.
我把那当作是毕生事业
I have made it my life's work
将迷失的灵魂引领回正规
to steer lost souls onto the path.
我从未想到会有一个学员
Not once did it occur to me that along would come a student...
能够如此全面  多方位地
who could so wholly and completely
释放我
set me free.
你也让我能完全释放  大师
You make me whole and free, too, Guru.
在我五个月前步入这个机构
I walked into this institute five months ago
一个迷茫的基督教女人
a clueless Christian woman...
名为Noomi…
named Noomi...
笃信人世间的光阴
who believed that life on Earth
只是跨入天堂前的历练
was just an audition to get into Heaven.
我从不知道世间也能如沐天堂
I never knew that life on Earth could be Heaven.
没有什么天堂  Noomi
There is no Heaven, Noomi.
只有当下
There is only the now.
当下即是人偶
And now be a doll and go pick out
去酒窖挑一瓶好酒吧
a nice bottle of red from the cellar
我去准备阿育吠陀泡沫浴
while I draw us an Ayurvedic foaming bath,
可以吗？
will you?
好的  大师
Yes, Guru.
啊！  啊！
Ah! Ah!
你是谁？  你想要什么？
Who are you? What do you want?
你认识这女人吗？
Do you know this woman?
她的名字是Sarah Newlin
Her name is Sarah Newlin.
我们有理由相信她就在这儿
We have reason to believe she is here.
我不能说谎
I cannot tell a lie.
是的  我知道她
Yes, I know her.
她在哪儿？
Where is she?
这个我不能告诉你
This I will not tell you.
那你还真是没用
How very unhelpful of you.
动手吧
Sarah Newlin!
Sookie  有人
Sookie, human.
- 哦  我的天啊  Holly - 嘿  你在这儿啊
- Oh, my God, Holly. - Hey there.
哦  我的天
Oh, my God.
- 你去哪儿了？ - 我不知道
- Where have you been? - I don't know.
- Sookie！  - Bill！
- Sookie! - Bill!
抓着这女的了！  拿下他！
We got the girl! Take him out!
去你的！
Fuck you!
- 都在这儿了？ - 我想是的
- That all of 'em? - Jason: I think so.
你他妈在想什么啊  Sookie？
What the fuck were you thinking, Sookie?
别回答我  别他妈说话  好吗？
Don't answer me. Do not fuckin' talk, all right?
你有吞下任何血吗？
You swallow any blood?
眼睛呢？进眼睛了吗？
What about your eyes? You get any in your eyes?
点头Yes  摇头No
Just shake your head yes or no.
靠！帮我带她去河里洗洗
Fuck! Help me wash her off in the river.
我来
I'm on it.
你
You.
你他妈在想什么  啊？
What the fuck were you thinking, huh?
告诉我说  我不能保护她和你吗?
Tell me I ain't good enough to protect her and you are
这是你想要的？
and this is what you come up with?
是她的主意  Alcide
It was her idea, Alcide.
我认识她够久  知道无法让她改变心意
I've known her long enough not to try and change her mind.
对  接着说  说我不了解她吗
Yeah, go on, tell me about Sookie like I don't know her.
我对天发誓  我他妈会宰了你
And I swear to God, I will fucking kill you.
Alcide!
Andy  树后边
Andy, behind the tree.
Alcide!
不  不  不！
No, no, no!
他还有气吗？
Is he breathing?
我可以…或有人可以帮你转化他
I could--or one of us could turn him for you,
但我们得…
but we would have to do it--
不
No.
你确定吗  Sook？
You sure, Sook?
之前也曾经历过
I've been down that road before.
救护车
Ambulance.
你扣下了扳机  Lou
You pulled the trigger, Lou.
我告诉过你  人生将因此改变
I told you life wasn't gonna be the same.
翻译是我  校对是我
Fanyi is me, Jiaodui is me
后期是我  监制还是我
Houqi is me, Jianzhi is me.
我已疯了  请为我点赞
I am fengle. Please Dianzan for me.
Alcide翘尾巴了  我为狼叔点蜡
Uncle-Lang wuhu le. Give langshu Lazhu.
我就是  真爱字幕组
I am TrueLove-SubGroup.
我是（新浪 百度）@幸福ing形式
wo  qu  chi  yao  le